in the next 60 days I'm gonna be turning
these hundred dollars into a million
dollars so in the next 60 days this is
going to be my only focus I wish all of
my money from my personal account and
I'm only going to be trading this 100
account until I take it to a million and
I'm putting everything on the line to
complete this challenge I'm putting my
reputation I'm putting my career at risk
just to complete this and I'm going to
be documenting and journeying every
single trade that I take and I'm gonna
put it here on YouTube every single week
and daily on my Instagram of how I'm
doing in this chat I'm gonna be showing
you guys the deposit the withdrawals of
every single trade that I take every
single week and most important is going
to be an audited account so it's going
to be as transparent as it can be and
for the initial start of this challenge
I've come all the way to Europe where I
literally came just so I get in sync
with the time zone so I can trade London
session in the morning and New York
session in the afternoon so I have no
excuses on why I don't achieve this
Challenge and this is going to be as
transparent as I guess I'm going to be
showing you guys the trades live during
my effects book all the trades that I
take and you guys are gonna follow along
with me every single trade and I'm gonna
also be sharing the trades on my
Instagram telegram Discord just to show
not only you guys here on YouTube but
every other community how I'm going to
be able to do on this challenge which is
very very selective on the type of
Trades that I take and one last thing
before we get started I want to disclose
that I am not going to be disclosing the
broker that I'm using simply because I
have no affiliation with them and I have
no control over what happens on the
platform so I don't want to be
responsible for sending thousands of
traders to a platform that I simply have
no affiliation and I have no control
over this is to protect my reputation
and most importantly to show you guys
how genuine I am as a person and that I
benefit from nothing other than my
trading because I can literally be
making hundreds of thousands of dollars
a month by affiliating with a broker and
I am not I'm just doing this for you
guys to show you guys that this is
possible any other person in my position
will take that deal in a heartbeat and
send everybody to a direction I'm not
doing it that's why I'm not going to be
disclosing the broker because I don't
want to be in responsibility of anything
and to show you guys how genuine I am as
a person so but that being said let's
get this haven't started all right so
now I'm going to explain to you guys a
little bit of how I'm going to exactly
turn the 100 into the mini I know this
might sound a little bit crazy but I've
been planning this for two months and
this is how I'm gonna do it so in order
for this to actually work my first four
winning trades have to be winners
because I'm trying to flip the 100 to
about four or five k and once I do that
I have enough room to cushion so I can
risk a little bit less and then I can
set it forget laundry with my trades so
I can flip the account in under 60 days
so my first four trades are very crucial
and I'm going to be very very selective
of what type of Trades I take and if I
survive this first challenge which is
the hardest of the whole entire
challenge I can have anywhere from three
to four thousand dollars by the end of
the week so my goal with the first unit
is to have around four to five hundred
dollars in profit then my second trade I
want to flip those four to 500 to about
a thousand two hundred and then on my
third trade I want to flip those
thousand two hundred to about 2500 and
on the portrait is with those 2500 to 5K
so we gotta make sure we get these solid
wooden trades by the time I get to the
5K okay I'm gonna lower my risk to about
25 per trade which you're getting
anywhere from a thousand to a thousand
two hundred fifty dollars per trip
[Music]
all right what's up guys so today is the
start of the 100 to the million the
official day that we have started so it
is currently right now July 24th 9 00
a.m GMT plus two so this would be around
3 A.M EST so we're about to start London
session and um as of right now count is
literally fresh 100 just deposited today
in the morning and this is exactly what
I'm going to be looking for the market
prediction right now so coincidentally
enough literally look at the time right
here it is 907 in the morning if we look
to the top right corner you see 908 in
the morning you guys can tell that this
trade right here literally is about to
get activated right now so basically
what I'm predicting to happen in this
trade right here is I'm just gonna look
for a little breakout Above This zone
right here because uh kind of once we
break out of this zone I'm expecting for
price to have a little push and then we
can kind of in a way get that little
quick momentum and then sell before it
comes back because you know we have to
be very aggressive at the beginning of
the challenge kind of like how I already
mentioned so I'm gonna wait for a little
breakout and and see what happens so
we'll check back in in like an hour and
see where it's at and I'm not gonna only
be trading One Market this week so I'm
thinking a very aggressive approach so
I'm going to be trading several markets
so I have more probabilities of passing
this so let me show you the different
markets I'm trading so the first one is
going to be GBP USD how we already
mentioned we're waiting for the breakout
of the zone to get a buy
um our next one would be GBP CAD which
we are waiting for pretty much the same
thing as the last fare which is waiting
for breakout to take the trade here we
are waiting for a little breakout to
take the trade I have the retreation to
go long literally the exact same thing
that happened right here I'm just
waiting for it to happen right here so
I'm gonna be waiting for a break Above
This Zone this is where I'll come and
I'll put an alarm so it notifies me that
it has broke in this area you notice
alarm is already set uh next we have AUD
JPY which I'm going to be waiting for a
rejection from this Zone to take the
trade where I will be going down to the
lower time frames and just waiting for
price to kind of come into this area
right here this line in order for me
trade next we have Euro USD where it's
the exact same thing I'm going to be
waiting for the break Above This Zone to
take the trade literally waiting for the
quick break above and if you notice it
is the same exact thing that I'm waiting
for on GBP USD but on Euro USD so if you
notice I'm looking at all of these
different markets but I'm having the
same approach the same strategy so this
is what makes me consistent I'm very
confident I'm gonna pass this chat
alright so update on the markets that
we're looking at today so it's one
o'clock Ibiza time it's 6 30 in the
morning Miami time so basically the
trades that we are looking to get in
would be GBP CAD which is the same trade
that we were looking at earlier what
we're looking at to enter once we put
the alarm for the breakout but now we're
at our next Zone be honest I buy at
these zones so I'm gonna wait for this
next hourly Candlestick to close which
is going to be the entry of New York
session so I'm looking to enter the
trade at this area next we have GBP USD
which we are waiting for the breakout to
break out of that zone number broke out
never took the trade is why we stick to
our plan after that we have AUD JPY
which I drew up that black line where I
wanted price to come back into that
black line in order for me to be
interested in the trade so right now I'm
gonna give it about another hour until
we enter New York sessions so like the
volume kicks in because we're just
ending London now and just to show you
guys still no trades on the account
still no trades so I'll keep you guys
updated all right so up there right now
it's about eight o'clock P.M here so we
are six hours back so it's 2 p.m EST
Miami time so updating you guys from the
trades from earlier that we're supposed
to take so gpp Cod we were looking to
buy at this area today in the morning
once we broke our alarm we didn't do
that we avoided one loss then we were
waiting for the price to come into this
next Zone to then look for buy so then
take the trade to the upside but my
entry signal never activated so didn't
end up taking the trade here avoided two
losses and then next we have GBP USD
we're looking for the buys earlier this
morning didn't break out so avoided a
third loss and then last but not least
AED JPY I was looking to buy at this
line right here if you guys remember
earlier from this morning didn't take it
because it just wasn't a high
probability trade so what I'm going to
do is I'm going to be waiting for a
pullback into this area right here in
order to actually take the trade to the
upside like that shows you guys the
Simplicity of to avoid losses in trading
the center forget strategy I just
avoided three losses because my first
trade has to be the best one because
it's the most important it's going to
get me out from that starting balance of
100 bucks to hopefully five six seven
eight hundred bucks and I could keep
compounding it so market update all
right so we're back uh it is currently
one in the morning Ibiza time and it is
650 EB show time so daily just the daily
Candlestick just closed one hour ago so
basically this is what we were looking
for earlier today remember however
earlier this morning we were at this
high and I'm expecting this pool back
into this area to take the trade long so
we're on our way to that area so I'm
gonna wait for the session to kick in
and then right here we have GBP USD
which I'm going to be waiting for now a
breakout of this zone right here in
order for me to take the trade to the
upside so I'm might be waiting for
someone of like a breakout like this
hopefully a London session in order for
me to take that trade and then we have
GBP CAD which I don't like it anymore
because of how this Daily Camera stick
close so as you guys can tell it is
currently right here Tuesday the 25th
1am and then right now we have
absolutely no trades on the account
still they're the same exact account no
trades as of right now so we'll update
tomorrow in the morning
all right so trade update it is 11 30 in
the morning here in Ibiza so the trade
is pulling back as we speak right now
we're probably up about 50 so I go here
we were probably like about 50. now
we're negative 12 I like how we're gonna
come back into this area and create the
next step notice the market Moves In
step I think it's just creating the next
higher low stop and have the next push
to the upside to start heading to the
upside hopefully we reject the zone and
uh so I forget if we lose this trade
we're gonna lose about anywhere 30 to
like 50 so we're gonna say what happens
and I update you in a little bit
all right I actually think we had to do
that in order to keep going up so
to see what happens hopefully I don't
below this account we're getting ready
to go to London
until I make money there way to London
but we gotta stop by Portugal in order
to pull it to London we couldn't get a
jet in time to go from here to London it
was cheap it was like 20K but we
couldn't find one because there's no
parking any Visa because the Visa is
packed all week because of summer or
whatever and then we gotta get on a
regular clean
all right so we're officially Landing in
the UK so we just landed in the UK right
now it is currently Tuesday it's 7 P.M
so it's probably like a two three hour
update from the last time we saw the
trade and now the account is up about
107 so it's the same exact trade that we
took so like this is the trade this is
where we were in the drawdown earlier no
stop loss because I just said but we're
going all the way in on one side because
I know how to predict the mark in the
direction perfectly now the tricky part
is just getting in and that's where I
have the seven forget strategy where I
teach the direction and how to enter so
right now we've created a higher high
I'm expecting for maybe another little
retracement for price to come back into
this area price comes back into this
area then I'll be looking to buy again
to continuation to the upside so far
[Music]
fun bloody hell trade update up about oh
oh
160 we're in London babies is that the
Big Ben
hey
what's going on let's see how the
Train's done oh we got one percent we
gotta check up tomorrow
all right so today it is Wednesday 9 25
GMT plus one so we're in London time
right now so basically instead of being
six hours ahead now we're five hours
ahead so that confused me a little bit
because now London starts at eight in
the morning not at nine so we ended up
catching a trade easy money remember how
yesterday I was explaining to you guys
how I was looking for a pullback in
order to take the trade to the upside
because I was explaining to you guys how
we had the higher high push we can then
have a retracement and then continue
going long well I didn't manage to get
in this retracement right here because I
just wasn't active during that session
and then I managed to get on the next
retracement here in the session that I
was looking into getting and if you
notice right here we managed to get in
on a very very nice little trade um not
much like if you guys look at the trade
right now it is up about 15 so I
literally couldn't take any more lot
sizes so basically right now I'm looking
to now enter Euro USD as well I'm
waiting for price to come back back into
this area to then head to the upside or
I'm going to then be waiting for a
breakout of this area to take the trade
and then GBP CAD remember how at the
beginning of the week I was explaining
how I wasn't looking for Longs here but
I was waiting for the break out of this
area to then go long well we had a
beautiful push to the upside and I'm
going to be waiting for the literally
the same thing that I was waiting for
here at the beginning of the week that
it didn't happen now I'm going to be
waiting for it here again so for now
we're gonna set and forget our GBP USD
trade and then uh I might close the
small position just to kind of build a
little bit of a margin in the account
but I update you guys throughout the day
so stay tuned alright so I'm gonna
explain to you exactly how I'm going to
do this with the risk management I got
to be at 5K by the end of August 4. so I
gotta start August 7th with 5K because
the challenge is supposed to be done on
September 24th because that's 60 days
from the day I started obviously if I go
over a week or two it doesn't matter but
the point is if I go from 5K to 10K 10K
to 20K 20K to 40K 40K to 80k 80k to 160
60 to 340 and then 340 to like six seven
hundred thousand and then from there
just do a quick flip to like a map pow
so it's probably going to take me like
70 days but I have to win every single
week and double up every single week
because I'm already doubled up I'm
already almost tripled up on this trade
actually doubled up so I just have to
get to the 5K once I get to the 5K it's
just double up from that point but to
get from here to the 5K I have to like
500x or what is it like 5000x we can do
it
[Music]
all right so trade up there right now it
is 240 uh London time so it's probably
like 9 40 Miami time so an update on the
trade is that we are currently still
bullish as of right now we have a like
we still have we're still in both trades
right we're still in this trade and we
took yesterday almost through the
account and then on the new one and then
currently right now let me show you guys
the trade that I predicted this morning
what I wanted to happen and how it's
happening again so I predicted I'd say
out of 10 moves probably like eight or
seven as you guys can tell right here
gvp CAD earlier this morning
um I predicted how I was waiting for the
breakout perfectly to the high of that
line now I'm waiting for the pullback to
take the trade to the upside uh GBP USD
we're gonna keep status for getting this
thing and then next would be Euro USD
how I'm waiting for the breakout of this
Zone to them by the trade so let's go
all right so trade update right now so
it is currently 5 26 so it's about 126
Miami time so the four hour Candlestick
just closed so as of right now we are
very much still bullish I am still in
both trades so I'm gonna be waiting for
the next probably four hours which is
the next daily Candlestick to close so
as you guys can tell we are still very
much still in this trade right here and
this one and then we are still in this
one right here and I'm gonna be holding
them for a little bit longer so these
are the results as of right now I'm up a
total of it's refreshing we got the 270
bucks so that's good all right so this
is why this this is why we came to
London so I can catch all of these
sessions so as of right now this is
still the same exact trade all we're
doing is we're setting we're getting
broke that's all we're doing right now
reading is supposed to be easy it's not
supposed to be hard so we're still
continuing the move as of right now
again we're still in the same exact
trade up about now
340.
and then you guys remember Euro USD from
this morning you guys can see here
you're a USD I was expecting for the
breakout to happen and then after we get
the breakout we're gonna get the
pullback exactly what we're having as of
right now so I'm gonna probably let the
other trades ride or actually get into
trade right here because like I said
this still has a upside room as you can
tell there's still plenty of room to
probably get my account into a nice
piece
[Music]
all right so trade up there right now we
just got back from dinner so it is 12 37
London time so this is how the trade is
currently looking so we had a very
strong push up now we're getting a
retracement so if it's bullish we should
keep doing the same thing little steps
to the upside but the only thing I don't
like how the daily time frame closed we
can probably see a big daily retracement
back into this area to then head back up
to the upside so I'm going to be waking
up in about five hours which is gonna be
uh 5 a.m uh London time which would be
12 o'clock Miami time and when I see how
the market is to see if I close the
trade pre-london session before it has
that push if it has that push so for now
we're gonna keep set of forgetting great
is still exactly the same we're up now
about around it's loading now we're up
about 260 bucks so still in route see
how it goes so we'll check in in the
morning
[Music]
all right so it is currently Thursday uh
nine in the morning in London and then
it's 4 a.m Miami time so I just come
here what time is it in Miami I refresh
the website refresh the website so it's
Thursday 27 410 if you add the five
hours from London and then this is the
trade right now following up from last
night exactly what I said
you guys can see right here last night
we were at this High I'm explaining all
right we're gonna have a retracement now
where we can potentially keep doing the
same exact thing that we're doing which
is creating the bullish Trend to the
upside and would you look at that
exactly what I said they ain't believing
us oh as of right now this is where the
trade is and I literally can't take
another trade because the leverage and
the margin doesn't let me but if I would
have been able to take more trades this
account would probably be at five six K
right now already because I would enter
at every single high or low that I
predicted and this is the next trade let
me just actually move this a little bit
to the right and then let me push this
to the upside so we are still in both of
these trades last night predicted this
pullback hit the upside and then next we
have your USD and if you guys notice it
is exactly what I said yesterday as well
so I literally said we're gonna wait for
the breakout once you wait for the
breakout you have to wait for the higher
low pullback to then go to the upside I
would have very much taken this trade as
well but I literally couldn't because my
account doesn't let me do the leverage
and the margin that I have so and I
would have tooken that trade along with
the other one but I'm already maxed out
on the capability of what that account
can take in trades like it's already at
the max there's no way I can take any
more positions due to the account size
so I have to wait till I close the trade
in order so I can take another trade so
predicted this one predict the GBP USD
continuation and predict
CAD where I expected this breakout then
the pullback to go long so everything as
of right now has been a hit usually what
I do is I'll pick two out of these three
trades on my regular account and just go
two three percent risk but on a big
account now kinda have to pick the best
one and just ride with it so for the
prediction for the rest of the day I
believe now it should continue to create
like it has a high probability of
continuing to create these higher lows
to the upside um but there is one thing
to keep in mind and that would be the
daily time frame that it can still have
that retracement so I might be closing
very soon because truthfully I am ahead
of schedule I want it to be by the end
of this week around 300 maybe so we're
at 500 so we're ahead of schedule so
we'll check in in about three four hours
time and then see what happens so I just
got asked right now to DM what would I
do if I were to start from zero with no
money and it's literally the same exact
thing that I already did because I
started for no money I was at Dunkin
Donuts five years ago and the first
things first no matter what is have a
vision like is this actually possible
the next thing would be get educated
learn there's no way you're going to
make money in any industry without
learning it's like same thing you're
going to go to the gym you're not going
to get fit if you don't learn about your
diet or you don't know about how to
actually work out and then the third
thing is have a crazy Obsession that
people think you're crazy doesn't matter
what your parents say doesn't matter
what your friends say your cousins uh
relatives your neighbor doesn't matter
you have to be so deep into the vision
and so deep into your own Journey that
you do not listen to any Outsiders
that's exactly what I did I was in like
a six to eight month dark mode where the
only person I talked to was myself
that's why I got the results that I have
today all right so trade update not
looking good great about a hit Margin
Call as you guys can tell we are about
70 dollars in a loss we're talking close
the trade right now we're back at almost
like starting balance but I'm honestly
just gonna wait to the Daily Candlestick
closes because as soon as the daily
Candlestick closes if it closes under
those bodies then it's a done deal the
trade is going to keep going down if it
closes above it has some faces still
going up so we got about three hours
left so update in three hours three
hours later all right so update from
yesterday's train count officially blown
it is what it is I'm not gonna lie I was
super greedy I was up almost 600 on this
trade which is more than my initial goal
I go with just the end off the week
anywhere from 200 to 3 400 and I was
well up over that and I didn't so I got
greedy but is what it is lesson learned
first attempt failed second attempt I'm
ready to go so we're already in our
second trade in our second attempt like
I literally just took this trade right
now it's gonna be GBP cat so let me let
me actually show so this is the exact
same trade that we've been looking to
buy whether it broke and retested above
when the broken retested above here or
if we were looking to buy here if it
ever gave me my entry signal as you can
tell we're back at this Zone this is the
secret the secret is to buy at a strong
area of Interest these are strong every
Ventures and right here you can see that
this is my new area of interest and I've
gotten my entry signal to enter this
trade as of right now so I'm not being
greedy anymore and I'm setting my take
profit as to what it should be so this
should have a nice push-up a little
retracement and then continue going to
the upside and this is currently how
that trade is looking on the new account
right now
hey there's nobody
bro the cars are coming this way
all right so trade up there right now
GBP CAD probably like two three hours
ago from the last time we updated it
exactly what I said I had this area of
Interest wait for the entry signal and
seven forget we're doing it again and
this time we learned you know I could
have gone a lot higher risk but as you
guys can tell here we're now 60 on this
brand new account like literally showed
you guys the trade live streams you guys
to trade the updates I'm going to show
you guys how I'm gonna close right
before the week close hopefully I can
make a little bit more um so I can be in
profit the amount that I need so I can
start off next week on fire so I can
flip it to a thousand and under two
three trades like this is not any more
legit than this I'm literally showing
you guys the trades before now
[Music]
being that old and having a Ferrari it's
not worth it you gotta have a Ferrari
when you're young now when you're old
like that guy guy probably can't even go
fast enough we are going to acai berry
in Kensington and Chelsea
is 247 Kings Road
247 King Drive
all right so trade updates we officially
closed the trade for Friday on the new
account so we are completely done with
the challenge today so as you guys can
tell it is currently two o'clock uh
London time is 9 A.M so I don't want to
hold the trade past 9 A.M Miami time
because the Market's about to close it's
on Friday rather get my profit to leave
so you guys can see here we're at 155
this is on one phone I'll show you guys
here on another phone this is another
phone which is the exact same thing
we're up to 55 I'm gonna show you guys
on my Facebook too and then this is our
my effects book which you kind of have
to wait for it to update the last time I
updated was two hours ago as you guys
can tell here this is the equity that
it's up 156 so this will probably
refresh and then a couple of minutes but
trade is done made 55 just today and
obviously we learned the lesson so I
blew the account yesterday and today I'm
already up 55 like trust me next week is
about to be fired because I'm coming in
10 times more focus and with the lessons
learned and on top of that we're going
to set up for getting all right so we're
gonna we're back on our way to the hotel
and let's do a quick recap of what
happened this week right there's a lot
to happen so it obviously started any
Visa where we were looking to take it by
on GBP USD and we're looking to sell
your USD we missed the first trade on
your USD and then we avoided two to
three losses at the beginning of the
week by simply waiting for the breakout
of the trade then after that on Tuesday
we ended up taking the trade on GBP USD
that started this whole entire challenge
the trade went up into profit probably
about 40 50 then it came down into
drawdown where we nearly blew the
account and as soon as we got on the
flight to go from Ibiza to Portugal and
from Portugal to the UK we landed in the
trade is about a hundred like twenty
dollars in profit so that's the power of
the center forget just at the beginning
of the chapter and then we managed to
take another trade on Thursday here in
Europe where we managed to get another
entry where it probably gave us probably
a total of positive Equity like 600 on
the account but then you know the market
reverse first I ended up getting a
little bit too greedy and holding the
trades too long it happens it was my
mistake not the markets I predicted that
I was going to pull back I didn't think
I was going to pull back that fast that
much I take full responsibility learn
from my mistakes and now we're gonna
apply that to this new account which
we're already up 55 in just one session
on a Friday like couple hours before the
market closed I mean 55 on a trade so
the two very important lessons that I
learned is that you cannot get greedy I
was getting very greedy with the trade
because I just wanted to make more money
and flip it to a thousand it was just
one movement and then the other lesson
that I learned was to stick to a
positive risk to reward a minimum of a
2.5 risk reward doesn't have to be any
more than that and let me show you guys
the performance of my second account
where I am already up 55 on just one
single trade a couple of hours before
the market closed so
um with the lessons learned that I had
on the first account and already
starting a positive I'm very excited for
what this week has to bring because I
think I'm ready to turn it up I think
we're going to close this next week
probably a thousand dollars thousand
five hundred in profit easy and I'm
gonna be back in my home office so let's
see how that goes all right so that's a
wrap for week one of the challenge I'll
see you guys next week where I'm gonna
be taking the 100 to a mill where it
gets even crazier than week one but make
sure if you guys want to make anywhere
from a thousand to a thousand five
hundred dollars a week with my seven
figure strategy just hit the link in the
description below there's a video there
that explains everything to you in
detail so you guys can not only follow
along my challenge but for you guys
hopefully one day you guys could turn
100 into a mill as well so make sure you
guys stay tuned to next week and I'll
see you guys there